* * *

* * *

Privacy Policy
==============

Effective Date: May 24, 2018

**Your privacy is important to us.** We want you to understand what we collect, what we don't collect, and what we do with the information you provide us. As a privacy-focused company, VPNElf will be as transparent as possible with our customers.

Summary
-------

* We are a zero-logging VPN service, meaning we’ll never track or store your data while connected to our VPN service.
* The only personal information we collect from you is used for your account setup, such as an email address and payment information.
* We will never sell your personal information to third parties.
* We use cookies on our Site to provide basic functionality and understand Site activity in aggregate. You can disable cookies on our Site at any time.

Privacy Policy Outline
----------------------

What do we collect?
-------------------

Our Privacy Policy (the "Policy") applies to the information we collect about visitors to [https://vpnelf.com](https://vpnelf.com/) (the "Site"), and subscribers to the VPNElf and related service (the "Services"), which are owned and operated by VPNElf. Let’s break down each aspect of our business to give you a better understanding of what we collect from you:

### Services

VPNElf does not collect or log any traffic of its Services, making us a **zero-logging VPN**.

To subscribe to our Services, we’ll need some basic information from you. When you create an account, we require the following limited information from users in order to process payments:

* An email address
* A payment method

Users who sign up for our Service using credit card will also be asked to provide:

* A full name
* A credit card
* A billing address

Once you’ve created an account, you can access and modify your billing and subscription information at any time via your control panel.

### Site

You do not have to give us any personally identifiable information to browse our Site. We collect basic information from visitors to our Site, such as the number of site visitors and page views. We detail this more in the "Cookies and Tracking" section below. We never track your activities outside of our Site, nor do we track your browsing activities when you’re logged into our VPN service.

VPNElf does not share your private information with any third parties aside from the disclosures already made in this privacy policy.

#### Cookies

To get a better understanding of how users access and use our Site, we may use or engage others to use cookies, and similar technologies. **You can browse our Site without telling us who you are or submitting any personal information.** We simply use this information to understand Site activity and to monitor and improve Site performance.

##### What are cookies?

VPNElf uses cookies to:

* Authenticate your account when you log into the Site;
* Aggregate statistical information about user activity;
* Help prevent fraud;

Cookies may be stored on your device to improve user experience across visits to our Site, and for analytics including page views and site visits. Keep in mind that this type of data does not distinguish an individual -- in other words, it won’t be tied to your identity. The cookies used for our Site are not used or tied to the VPN service itself, so your activity within our Services is completely private.

##### How do I disable cookies?

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but if you prefer, you can edit your browser options to block them in the future. The “Help” portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your computer from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Site visitors who disable their web browsers' ability to accept cookies will be able to browse the Site, but certain Site features will not function.

| Source | Listing | About | Opt Out |
| --- | --- | --- | --- |
| Google Analytics | ssl-googleanalytics.com | [Learn More](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245) | [Disable](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) |
| Bing | bat.bing.com | [Learn More](https://help.bingads.microsoft.com/#apex/3/en/53056/2) | [Disable](http://choice.microsoft.com/en-us/opt-out) |
| Facebook | staticxx.facebook.com www.facebook.com | [Learn More](https://www.facebook.com/help/403786193017893) | [Disable](https://www.facebook.com/help/211829542181913) |
| Shareaholic | Apps.shareaholic.com analytics.shareaholic.com | [Learn More](https://support.shareaholic.com/hc/en-us) | [Disable](https://support.shareaholic.com/hc/en-us/articles/201441496-Cookie-Consent-for-EU-Visitors) |
| Twitter | platform.twitter.com analytics.twitter.com t.co | [Learn More](https://help.twitter.com/en/rules-and-policies/twitter-cookies#) | [Disable](https://twitter.com/settings/personalization) |
| DoubleClick by Google | stats.g.doubleclick.net | [Learn More](https://www.doubleclickbygoogle.com/) | [Disable](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated) |
| New Relic | bam.nr-data.net js-agent.newrelic.com | [Learn More](https://support.newrelic.com/) | [Disable](https://docs.newrelic.com/docs/browser/new-relic-browser/installation/disable-browser-monitoring) |

#### Third Parties

We engage third parties to view and analyze Site data that’s not personally identifiable to you. These third parties use cookies on our Site to collect, analyze, and generate reports on Site usage for us. **We do not provide these third parties with any personal information about you.**

| Provider | Service | About |
| --- | --- | --- |
| ReliableHosting | Website hosting | [Learn More](https://reliablehosting.com/privacy.htm) |
| ZenDesk | Support ticket system Live chat | [Learn More](https://www.zendesk.com/company/customers-partners/cookie-policy/) |
| SendGrid | Email | [Learn More](https://sendgrid.com/) |
| WPEngine | Blog hosting | [Learn More](https://wpengine.com/legal/privacy/) |
| MaxMind | Security and fraud detection services | [Learn More](https://support.maxmind.com/) |

How do we use your information?
-------------------------------

The information we collect through our Site is used for the following reasons:

* To create new accounts
* Collect payment for our Services
* Communicate with current subscribers
* Offer troubleshooting or customer support

We promise to never sell or share personal information with third parties, and we’ll never log your browsing activity.

How To Modify Your Personal Information
---------------------------------------

If you’d like to review or amend your account information, or for technical support, service information, and changes in usage, please contact: [\[email protected\]](https://vpnelf.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). We respond to all requests in a timely manner, and we’re always happy to assist you. You may also view and amend much of your account information, or update or renew your subscription, by logging in to your account and updating your account information.

Emails
------

We may send you marketing and promotional emails about products, services, and other information we think may interest you.

If you receive a marketing or promotional email from us, you may click the ‘Unsubscribe’ link contained in the bottom of every email to "opt out" from future promotional emails. However, we may continue to send you emails about your account and for other purposes related to customer service. You may also unsubscribe from such emails at any time by emailing us at [\[email protected\]](https://vpnelf.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) and telling us you would like to "unsubscribe from marketing emails."

We also send product awareness emails to new customers. These emails include application tips and other information intended to educate VPNElf account subscribers about the uses and fundamentals of a VPN.

### Transactional Emails

#### Account

To keep you updated on any changes or alerts related to your account, we will occasionally send you account information emails. This includes:

* Account setup confirmation
* Registration
* Password reset

#### Billing

Billing emails allow us to relay important information to you about your transactions. This includes:

* Credit card expiration alerts
* Payment method questions
* Purchase confirmations

Transactional emails are system-generated and simply serve the purpose of alerting our customers when necessary. Please be aware that if you have opted out of our marketing emails, you will still receive transactional emails from time to time.

Children's Privacy
------------------

Our Site and Services are not intended for anyone under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and believe that your child under 13 has provided personal information to us, please contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://vpnelf.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) so that we can delete the child's information. No information is collected from children from the ages of 13 to 18 years old

Security Measures We Have In Place
----------------------------------

**The security of our customers is our priority.** We use security measures that are consistent with industry standards to protect your personal information from loss, theft, misuse or unauthorized access or disclosure or destruction. All of our employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. In addition, access to user or subscriber personal information is restricted to those who need to know such information to perform their job functions.

We use encryption, access controls, passwords, and/or physical security measures to protect the basic information we collect against unauthorized access and disclosure.

GDPR
----

The European Union General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) is effective as of May 25, 2018. This regulation broadens the privacy rights that EU individuals have over how their personal data is collected, processed, and maintained.

Dedicated IP Addresses
----------------------

We want our customers to be aware that while we offered packages with dedicated IP addresses in the past, these packages were not designed for anonymity, and should not be used for that purpose. Dedicated IP addresses are built for security and region-switching, and are assigned to one customer for their exclusive use. For additional privacy and anonymity, we recommend switching to our current VPN packages that use our shared IP network. These plans give you access to more regions and provide another layer of privacy. If you’re a current customer on a legacy plan with a dedicated IP, you can upgrade your account at no charge. Please contact [\[email protected\]](https://vpnelf.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) to change your account.

Privacy Settings and Requests
-----------------------------

VPNElf provides information about our data privacy policies, including how we use cookies, in the Privacy section of this website. We also provide tools on this website that allow users to control privacy preferences for certain aspects of using this site or interacting with VPNElf, such as for cookies and marketing. If you have any data privacy or personal data questions or requests, please contact [\[email protected\]](https://vpnelf.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

How to Contact Us
-----------------

For questions about this Site or VPNElf Services, or for more information about how we or our business operators treat your personal information, please contact us at: [\[email protected\]](https://vpnelf.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Changes to This Policy
----------------------

From time to time, we may change and/or update this Privacy Policy. We recommend you regularly review this page for updates.

### 

Need Help? Call: +44 (1621) 736841 | Email: [\[email protected\]](https://vpnelf.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

##### General

##### Download

##### Policy

##### Supported Payment Methods

Copyright © 2018 Monzonite Limited | 50 High Street, Office 2, 2nd Floor, Maldon, Essex, United Kingdom, CM9 5PN
